hi everybody and welcome to this session
大家好，欢迎参加本次会议
where we're going to talk about
我们要谈的地方
breakthroughs and machine learning I'm
突破和机器学习我是
Laurence Moroney I'm a developer
Laurence Moroney我是开发人员
advocate at Google are working on
谷歌的倡导者正在努力
tensorflow with the Google brain team
与Google大脑团队的tensorflow
we're here today to talk about the
我们今天在这里谈谈
revolution that's going on in machine
在机器中发生的革命
learning and how that revolution is
学习和革命是怎样的
transformative now
现在变革了
I come from a software development
我来自软件开发
background any software developers here
在这里任何软件开发人员
given that at i/o sure and this is this
鉴于在i / o肯定，这就是这个
transformation this revolution is
改革这场革命是
particularly from a developer's
特别是来自开发者的
perspective is really really cool
透视真的很酷
because it's giving us a whole new set
因为它给了我们一整套新的东西
of tools that we can use to build
我们可以用来构建的工具
scenarios and to build solutions for
场景并为其构建解决方案
problems that may have been too complex
可能过于复杂的问题
to even consider prior to this it's also
甚至在此之前考虑它也是
leading to massive advances in our
导致我们的大量进步
understanding of things like the
理解像这样的事情
universe around us it's opening up new
我们身边的宇宙正在开辟新的世界
fields in arts and it's impacting and
艺术领域，它的影响和影响
revolutionising things such as
彻底改变诸如此类的事物
healthcare and so many more things so
医疗保健等等
should we take a look at some of these
我们应该看看其中的一些
so first of all astronomy at school I
首先是学校的天文学I
studied physics I wasn't the comm site
学习物理我不是通讯网站
person so I'm a physics and astronomy
所以我是物理学和天文学
geek and it wasn't that long ago when we
极客和我们不久前不久
learned how to discover what new how new
学会了如何发现新的新东西
planets around other stars in our galaxy
我们银河系中其他恒星周围的行星
and what the way that we discovered it
以及我们发现它的方式
was that sometimes would observe like a
是有时会像一个人一样观察
little wobble in the star and that meant
这个明星里有点摇晃，这意味着什么
that there was a very large planet like
有一个非常大的行星像
Jupiter size or even bigger
木星大小甚至更大
orbiting that star very closely and
绕着那颗恒星非常接近地运转
causing a wobble because of the
因为这个引起了一阵晃动
gravitational attraction but of course
引力吸引力但当然
the kind of planets we want to find out
我们想要找出的那种行星
the small rocky ones like our earth on
像我们的地球一样的小岩石
Mars where you know there's a chance of
火星，你知道有机会
finding life on these planets and
在这些星球上寻找生命
finding those and discovering those was
找到那些并发现那些是
very very difficult to do because small
很难做到因为小
ones close to the star you just wouldn't
那些靠近星星的你不会
see but there's with research that's
看，但有研究的是
been going on in the Kepler mission
在开普勒任务中继续进行
they've actually recently discovered
他们最近发现了
this planet called Kepler 90i
这个星球叫做开普勒90i
by sifting through data and building
通过筛选数据和建立
models for using machine learning and
使用机器学习和模型的模型
using tensorflow and Kepler 90i is
使用tensorflow和开普勒90i是
actually much closer to its host star
实际上更接近它的主星
than Earth is so that its orbit is only